And the big question: does the
advertising promise hold true without Qualim?
Honestly, making campfire bread or sitting comfortably around a
fire is a really great
thing and super cozy.  It smells awful, it
stinks, and the children smell as if they've
spent the night in a smokehouse.  This fire bowl is meant to
be different.  If you want, you can
even grill on it.  So today we're going to test a
real fire with dry wood,
and then we'll put a
nice bratwurst on it.  Unlike my
colleague, this one works with pellets,
coal and wood.  And the big question: does
the advertising promise of no smoke hold true?
First of all, thank you for tuning in.  This item
currently costs €147, and I think you can
find it even cheaper.  Don't worry,
everything is linked below the video or
you can scan the QR code.  Let's
quickly light some kindling
and take a closer look at the fire bowl
, because it has a
special feature that, as you can see, the one in the
back doesn't have.  Because what's
smoking here is wood gas, and the
smokeless fire bowl has a
special feature.  Firstly, it has a
special ventilation system with drafts,
and secondly, these holes on the
sides, which ensure that
this smoke does not form.  I've
already tested this on a small scale.
I don't know if this works on a large scale
or if it only helps the manufacturer.
This is definitely a very well-
ventilated system.
We can remove the ash from underneath, and the
metal grate is really thick and sturdy, just as
you would expect from a good grill
.